I
I like this car. How much is it? If you have to ask you can't afford it try me
240,000
This should cover
We take it for a test drive
Oh
Cool right cow like it
Okay, maybe really feel no
Someplace I'm trying to forget
I'm me, too
It is that birthmark
Oh
It's pretty big for a birthmark. Don't touch
Ow! That'll hurt
Jerk
What's the deal Cal?
Every night you're on here at the bay, but you always leave empty-handed
What are you a monk or something?
What's the point of starting something if it's just gonna end badly?
Is no mystery?
Turquoise
It's lightly impaled
went down
It may even be uh
optic
all with energy
solid bullish
banged on aографica
doubleق, fertig
Okay.
Hello?
Clark, is that you?
Please come home.
Oh.
Somebody save me.
Let your warm hands break right through me.
Don't care how you do it.
Just stay, stay.
Come on.
I've been waiting for you.
Just stay.
I've made this whole world shine for you.
Stay, stay.
Come on.
Everyone on the floor now.
Get down.
Get down now.
Don't move.
You two are fucking what?
What you got to do?
Don't go down.
Let me get down.
You got to go.
Don't move.
Light the floor.
Get down.
Stay down.
Face down.
Get to floor.
Get far off there.
Shoot the bastard.
Stick to balloon animals.
Sorry, Krusty.
I saw the bank first.
My lifestyle determines my death style.
Keep searching.
Keep on searching.
Put your hands in the air.
Krusty, come on.
We're going to find your head.
Keep on searching.
Drop the bag.
You're flying a plane.
Keep on searching.
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
Kick the red.
Do you want a minute?
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
Check it out!
廖
менее
Si I'm a charging engine.
This control,
and my life might be different.
Tick, tick.
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tock, hey!
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tock!
These crimes just keep getting bigger and bigger.
We can't be sure it's Clark.
Look, I know you don't want to believe, but it's him.
What are we going to do?
There really isn't anything.
Yeah.
You get in the truck.
I'm going to get my coat.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get him.
He knows what Red Kryptonite does.
He can take that ring off any time.
Martha, I don't know that.
Jonathan, the phone calls.
They're the first step.
I can't just sit around in this farmhouse
and do nothing anymore.
Even if you find him, how exactly do you
plan on bringing him home?
It's been three months.
We've been searching all that time.
We filed a missing persons report.
We have done everything.
We can.
Martha.
The fact is Clark doesn't want to be found.
He'll come home to us when he's ready.
We just have to have faith.
OK.
Hey.
Haven't seen you in a while.
I'm sorry.
I haven't seen you in like a week.
I was wondering if we still lived under the same roof.
I'm swamped here.
Your dad says you spent the entire afternoon
at the Daily Planet.
Yeah, as far as my editor's concerned,
picking up his dry cleaning is more of a priority
than meeting face to face with the junior columnist.
I thought maybe we could have lunch.
I can't.
Is Lex gone?
Talon's been relegated to Luther Corp accountants
who have no interest in a coffee shop in Smallville.
OK.
Well, if you need a ride to Lex's funeral,
I'm always available for chauffeuring.
And moral support.
Thanks.
I'm going with the Kents.
Have you heard from Clark?
I was thinking of staying in Metropolis
with Nell for a few days.
Feel guilty I haven't spent more time searching for him.
He's not lost, Lana.
You may have written him off, but I can't give up hope.
Clark ran away.
He made a conscious decision to leave his friends, his family,
and the girl he claimed to love.
To hell with him, teenage vedere.
L القرنئ أنت، Lئimiento tienes que aprender.
And what happened is because of traffickers.
Took you more time alone than you could take out your unit.
Ron Brooke neverけれ.
And I'm worried about you.
Me neither.
I'm not worried.
Listen.
You okay?
You did get away with it.
I'm sorry.
Who sent you?
I did.
Morgan Edge.
Sent out his car.
How'd you get it?
My dad's a real bastard.
What do you want?
You came to my club
flashing money
and then you interrupted
my guys at the bank.
I take it that that was not
a coincidence.
Those clowns,
they work for you?
You've made quite a reputation
for yourself.
I set up this test
so I could see with my own eyes
if you were man or myth.
I clearly hear both.
Well, I'm glad I could
clear it up.
I'm glad I could clear it up for you,
Mr. Edge.
I'd like to talk about
a job opportunity.
Thanks, but
I'm really not looking for work right now.
I'd like to fly solo.
No matter how many bullets
bounce off you, Cal,
I'm still a kid.
And I'm the biggest crime boss
of Metropolis.
Well, I would think
you could afford better help.
I'm sorry.
That's why we're talking.
I've got this one job.
It'll make you
might as rich.
So when you are tired
of playing the little league,
you know where to find me.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Luther?
Mr. Luther, I got your message.
I admit I was surprised to hear that you wanted to meet today,
considering the fact that tomorrow is Lex's...
My son is gone, Miss Sullivan,
and there is nothing I can do now but put his memory to rest
and get on with the business of living.
You remember there used to be an octagonal keyhole here.
Vaguely. I didn't spend much time in this cave.
Trust me, it was right here.
It disappeared the same day as that inexplicable explosion on the Kent farm.
The same day that our young friend Clark went into exile.
You haven't seen him.
Have you?
After the fight that Clark and I had, I'd be the last person he'd call.
I've enjoyed reading your column, Miss Sullivan.
You're a good writer.
The worst sin of age is to forget the trials of youth.
I just wish that report you did for me on Clark Kent had the same kind of insight.
Well, I gave you everything I had.
But you came to me with such vigor.
Now it seems your enthusiasm for our arrangement is waning.
It's kind of hard to find information when the subject is M.I.A.
I'd hope you'd view that as a test of your reporter's mettle.
You're such a promising young talent.
I'd hate to see an opportunity like this vanish like the keyhole on this wall here.
Threatening me, Mr. Luther, isn't going to make Clark magically reappear.
All decisions...
have consequences.
Clark chose to run away from his.
You gonna run away from yours too?
Miss Sullivan?
Share them.
Call Dead Southern, interpret their latest mass 7660 damage report...
and get their ass back.
Atlanta City Standard.
Carter Smith.
sta, escrito la senca.
Imagine Clark speaking in .
Always gonna go.
This time, you and coaching.
SARAH MILLER
You here, cristiana?
TODAY
Always this pace, man.
This twice a week every day...
blah, blah, blah, blah.
We don't play politics at all.
No watch out.
You were calling her name again.
Who?
That bitch who set you up.
Louis, I appreciate everything you've done for me.
If you ever refer to my wife that way again,
I won't be held responsible for my actions.
See, I was just sitting here running through your story in my head.
Now you wake up, Helen and the pilot are gone,
and you're left to die.
You've got to at least consider the possibility.
Don't you have anything else to talk about?
All these years alone on an island?
Not really.
Why don't you go work on the raft?
Because I am not going to let you commit suicide.
You could end up drifting for weeks and die alone.
Is that what you want?
I want to get off this island and find out the truth.
Well, the truth.
See, the way I figure it,
either your father...
...set you both up,
Helen managed this on her own,
or the two of them were in league.
Why are you in such a hurry to get back to a family that twisted?
Because my life is not here.
Well, it doesn't sound so great back there.
You've got to stop looking at this place as a curse, Lex.
Shut up!
It is a gift!
Your life has been stripped down to its bare essence.
For the outside world, you're already dead.
Why don't you let your own self rest in peace?
I think the cruelest fate that a parent can suffer...
...is to lose a child.
Lex was touched with greatness.
We'd only just begun to see that potential.
I can only imagine the heights he would have soared to if his life...
...hadn't been...
...cut short so tragically.
These rituals are meant to bring closure.
But there's so many unanswered questions about Lex's disappearance.
Questions, I hope, that will someday be answered.
But those answers won't bring it back.
I would have searched for a thousand years if I thought I could be found.
I can't hold on to the past.
I'm not sure I can.
In my heart, I will be searching for my son forever.
So will I.
If you're here to grandstand for the paparazzi, I will have you escorted out.
I wish to hand my last respects to my husband.
Then Mrs. Luther, allow me to leave.
Before the hypocrisy begins.
Clark, I need to talk to you about...
Chloe, I told you to never come back here again!
Who else knows him?
No one. Your secret's safe with me, but we need to talk.
I'm busy.
Well, I'm coming in.
Now, what's your deal?
You come to Metropolis and you're a completely different person.
Maybe it's the real me.
Well, if it is, then I definitely prefer the country, Clark.
Now...
How did you afford all of this?
Why, Chloe?
So you can put me in your column or write a big story about me?
Maybe that's why you kept my secret.
I kept your secret because you asked me to.
I was hoping that if I left you alone, you'd get a grip and come home.
Now, there are people in Smallville that still haven't given up on the search.
I've erased Smallville from my past.
Really? Is that why you're still wearing your school ring?
You know, sooner or later, someone else is gonna find you.
You're lucky.
Maybe so.
But what are you gonna do if one day Lana shows up on your doorstep? Or your dad?
How are you gonna explain this to them?
I'm through explaining myself to anyone.
Clark, Lana is a wreck and your parents are losing the farm.
What do I care? I'm never gonna go back anyway.
Clark, you were not forced into exile.
You ran away from your problems. You are not being noble. You're being a coward.
Chloe, get out!
If you tell anyone where I am, I will go so far away from Metropolis that no one will ever find me.
I don't even know who you are anymore.
Get out!
The highlight of the day.
The somber affair was the performance of the grieving widow played to perfection by Dr. Helen Bryce in her first public appearance since her dramatic rescue.
I want you out of my house.
You can drop the act, Helen. You're among family.
And it's not your house yet.
I'm sure you didn't come all this way for a condolence call.
I won't give my condolences to a murderer.
I didn't murder Lex.
Oh, oh, that's right. Let me see if I can remember.
Your account of the harrowing event.
You woke up having been robbed, found the pilot jumping out of the airplane with only one parachute left.
Lex valiantly offered to give it to you and went down to his death in the crippled aircraft.
That's a wonderful piece of fiction.
I think the police would find it interesting that you hired me to spy on Lex.
You murdered my son. I won't rest till I've brought your duplicity.
I'll be to light.
You know, Helen, black widows may be powerful predators, but every predator is...
...somebody else's prey.
Ha!
Rush! Rush!
There's a plane!
Did you hear it?
I heard it.
What's your problem?
It's been going over in months.
It's too late now. It's long gone.
Ugh.
That's great!
God, that shit's great!
You're wasting your time. They're never gonna see you.
Son of a bitch.
I need to get off this island!
Ugh.
You know in your heart this is where you belong.
Now you can rage against it,
but ultimately you'll have to accept it.
I'm done.
Stay away from me, you freak.
I spoke to the bank.
They still want us out before the auction.
You know, it is amazing how you can fit your whole...
life into the back of a pickup truck.
Is Bill Ross still okay with us
storing our stuff in his garage?
Yeah. He said as long as we need it,
it's fine with him.
Oh, Lana gave me the keys to the apartment
over the town.
Great.
Yeah, it's small.
Okay, okay, Martha, Martha, Martha.
Martha, Martha, Martha.
Whew.
It's just not fair.
This farm has been in your family for three generations.
Four, counting Clark.
Sit down.
Please.
Since when have our lives been fair anyway, huh?
Do you remember the day
we found out we couldn't have children?
You grabbed my hand
and you told me not to worry.
You said that we would have happy days again.
And you were right.
We have had happy days.
With Clark.
But even though he's not here with us anymore,
Martha Kent, I am here to tell you
that we will have happy days again.
Mary.
Mary?
T evet,
Isn't it all right a relationshipURSE
that's made of nein?
Believe everything.
Fill the room.
Thank you.
Lana, hey, the other day, I, uh,
I didn't mean to push my own personal brand of self-denial on you.
It's okay, Chloe.
We're all dealing with Clark in our own way.
Yeah, and my way is to pull the emotional ripcord
and pretend like it didn't happen.
It's a force of habit when people walk out on my life.
I can't give up on him without a fight.
I already blew it once.
Blew it?
How?
When Clark was leaving, he asked me to go with him.
I said no, but I can't help thinking that if I had gone,
I could have convinced him to come home.
Lana, you can't save someone who doesn't want to be saved.
I love him.
It's okay.
Hey, your feelings for Clark aren't exactly breaking news.
I saw him yesterday.
Just for a second at Lex's funeral.
Are you sure?
Positive.
But he took off right away.
I'm gonna go back up there and post these.
Could you give me a lift?
Sure, but you don't need the flyers.
I know where he is.
What?
Yeah, okay, you're gonna totally hate me for this,
but I found him two months ago,
and I'm gonna have to go.
I'm gonna have to go.
Some friends of mine from the planet snuck me into this club, and there he was.
And I couldn't believe it was him, so I followed him back to his apartment.
You've known where he's been this entire time and you haven't said anything to anybody?
Well, I didn't have a choice. He said if anyone else found out, he'd run away to somewhere no one would find him.
I can't believe you've been telling me to give up on him.
Lana, he's not acting like himself. He could be dangerous.
Just give me the address.
Well, I'll take you.
No, I think you've done enough already.
I saw marriage lies, cause we don't talk dreams.
And football teams are kissing queens and eggs and salad.
What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
Clark, you need to come home.
Smallville's not my home anymore.
I'm calling an angel.
I am not letting you ride out of my life again.
Then get on.
Lex, I'd like you to meet my dad.
You killed your father.
Yeah, it was inevitable.
I had to do it. Only one of us could survive.
See, back there, he was a rich and powerful guy.
He was always criticizing me, never thinking I was good enough.
But it just kept chipping away, chipping away,
till there was nothing left.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I love strawberries.
I thought you and I were kindred spirits.
No, Louis.
You're a psychopath.
Well, there's one in all of us.
I'd just like mine now.
You don't have to come with me tonight, Louis,
otherwise I'll be the voir-able.
Take me with you.
This time, you're leaving with me,
and I'm leaving you with me too, come on.
I love strangers.
I love kids too.
I love you.
Hey, what's up, Cal?
Why'd she call you Cal?
It's my secret identity.
Clark! Clark!
I have been worried about you for three months
and you've been hanging around in nightclubs?
You're so cute when you're angry.
Lana, if you keep talking about Hicksville,
you're gonna be on the next bus going back.
I thought you were here to have some fun.
What's up, Cal?
Hey, what's up?
You're right. Sorry. I'll go freshen up.
Hey, why?
I think you look great.
I'm glad you're here.
Me too.
Well, if she's the one you've been saving yourself for,
I can understand the wait.
You're cries are real,
but your chances show it's real.
Not at all.
No.
Hello?
Mr. Kent, I found Clark.
Lana, where are you?
Nightclub in Metropolis called Atlantis.
See, he's acting really strange.
Lana, listen to me.
Clark is not himself right now.
I want you to be very careful.
Now, I'm on my way down there,
but if he wants to leave, I don't want you to try and stop him.
Okay.
Who are you talking to?
Who's this?
Clark, it's me.
Jonathan.
How's it far?
Clark, your mother and I love you very much,
and we want you to come home.
Is that right?
Hey, what about not dwelling on the past
and making a fresh new start?
Come on, you can admit it.
You're happier I'm gone.
Clark.
Son, that's not true.
I'm not your son,
and you're not my parents.
You never have been.
You never will be.
Clark, what is the matter with you?
Your parents love you.
I love you.
Do you always betray the people you love?
I've got to go get him.
How, Jonathan?
If he sees you, he could either run,
or if he's angry enough, he could hurt you.
You can't stop him.
Martha, if I don't go and get him now,
we may lose him forever.
I'm glad you decided to consider my offer.
Why the change of heart?
My past is catching up to my present.
I need to disappear.
Ready tonight?
My calendar just opened up.
There's an account in Grand Cayman.
Here's how much is waiting for you.
Oh.
That's a serious amount of zero.
Zeroes.
It's a serious job.
I need you to break into a secure building.
The office on the 60th floor has a very valuable package.
It's in a titanium reinforced steel safe.
Not a job for mere mortals.
Sounds like easy money.
I haven't told you where you're going yet.
Luther Core Plaza.
You want me to break into Lionel Luther's office?
Will that be a problem?
No.
It'll be my pleasure.
Lex!
I know.
I know every inch of this island.
Where are you going?
You can't kill me.
Damn on.
What's the difference?
I need some gun.
What happened?
I had to do it.
He was crazy.
I had no choice.
I had to kill him.
Kill who?
Him!
There ain't nobody there, man.
I'm adjustin'.
Cal, will ya.
No.
No!
Lewis!
These islands could mess with your head.
Play tricks, man.
You're lucky my captain saw your fire.
No.
What?
It was real.
You have to believe me.
He was real!
He was real.
He wasn't ready!
But you, you had to keep pushing him anyway, didn't you?
What kind of a race are you people?
No wonder you destroyed yourselves.
No, I didn't.
No!
I am Jor-El,
the true father of Kal-El.
His name is Clark Kent.
I am his father.
I raised him.
You have fulfilled your function in Kal-El's destiny.
His destiny is whatever...
Whatever he makes of it.
His destiny is too great for you to comprehend.
This was Kal-El's first test to see if he was ready to begin his journey.
He's too young.
He needs more time.
This phase of Kal-El's journey is almost complete.
It will be of no consequence if he returns to you for now.
You'll bring him home?
If you want him, you must retrieve him yourself.
No.
I can't.
He's too powerful.
Are you willing to sacrifice anything to get him back?
Yes.
For my son, I'll do anything.
No!
K.O.
Hello, Clark.
Jonathan Kent.
Isn't it a little past your bedtime?
How'd you find me?
Your biological father.
Your father?
You two are working together now, huh?
That's cute.
But I didn't listen to him, and I'm certainly not gonna listen to you.
Clark.
You need to put all this behind you, son.
Come on home to the people who love you.
Come on.
You should have stayed in Smalls.
All of them.
Son.
You're coming home with me.
Now.
Oh, my God!
You're coming home!
I love you.
You're all mine.
You look at me.
Thank you.